But give the Dems some credit,
at least they're finally recognizing
that their typical male supporter
is a smelly life support system for a man bun.
I mean, you know you're in trouble
when your Rambo is Beto O'Rourke.
And if this is your party's answer to Clint Eastwood,
no wonder Democrat men start menstruating.
And this is your action hero?
He banged the first girl who ever talked to him.
And she did it because she was a spy.
Now, it's good they're hitting the gym,
but we do it for ourselves, not for political advantage.
There's a difference there.
Republicans go because we like work,
we like strength, we like winning,
we like women doing lunges and Lululemons.
And look, I mean, look at me.
You think all this happens without hours at the gym?
Shout out to my personal trainer, it's Seth.
Yeah, don't wait up.